<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Skyblock Bazaar Status</string>
    <string name="app_id">839294731515</string>
    <!--achievement Simple Geometry-->
    <string name="achievement_simple_geometry" translatable="false">CgkI-4n1zrYYEAIQAA</string>
    <!--achievement Civics 101-->
    <string name="achievement_civics_101" translatable="false">CgkI-4n1zrYYEAIQAQ</string>
    <!--achievement Birthday Paradox-->
    <string name="achievement_birthday_paradox" translatable="false">CgkI-4n1zrYYEAIQAg</string>
    <!--achievement Everything Else Is Accelerating Up-->
    <string name="achievement_everything_else_is_accelerating_up" translatable="false">CgkI-4n1zrYYEAIQAw</string>
    <!--achievement Life Not As We Know It-->
    <string name="achievement_life_not_as_we_know_it" translatable="false">CgkI-4n1zrYYEAIQCA</string>
    <!--achievement Market Manipulation-->
    <string name="achievement_market_manipulation" translatable="false">CgkI-4n1zrYYEAIQBA</string>
    <!--achievement Pattern Recognizer-->
    <string name="achievement_pattern_recognizer" translatable="false">CgkI-4n1zrYYEAIQBQ</string>
    <!--achievement No Luck Required-->
    <string name="achievement_no_luck_required" translatable="false">CgkI-4n1zrYYEAIQBg</string>
    <!--achievement Order In Chaos-->
    <string name="achievement_order_in_chaos" translatable="false">CgkI-4n1zrYYEAIQBw</string>
    <!--leaderboard Most Coins Earned-->
    <string name="leaderboard_most_coins_earned" translatable="false">CgkI-4n1zrYYEAIQCQ</string>
    <!--leaderboard Most Active Users-->
    <string name="leaderboard_most_active_users" translatable="false">CgkI-4n1zrYYEAIQCw</string>
    <string name="api_key">Enter your Skyblock API key here</string>
    <string name="first_time">Hey, looks like this is your first time using this app:</string>
    <string name="key_instructions">In order to get your Skyblock API Key, log into skyblock, and type in /api.\n
        It will then tell you to type in \n/api new. Take that key and paste it in the box above.\n
        I recommend saving the key somewhere on your computer as well so you don\'t need to keep making new ones.\n
        (Though if you lose it, no worries, you should be able to just type in /api new again when you login and it\'ll make you a new one)</string>
    <string name="dummy_instructions">press this button once you do</string>
    <string name="preference_api_key">APIKey</string>
    <string name="url_beginning">https://api.hypixel.net/skyblock/bazaar</string>
    <string name="button_fail">Enter a valid key first</string>'
    <string name="button_success">Key works! Press this button again to begin.</string>
    <string name="loading_msg">Currently loading</string>
    <string name="current_as_of">Prices updated on:\n</string>
    <string name="interviewer_message">Welcome to my app!\n
        Although this app was designed for players of a minecraft server called Hypixel Skyblock,
        I also made it as a demonstration of my coding ability. \n
        I learned how to do everything in this app in just one summer during the covid when I could\'nt find any other job.\n
        This app won\'t be super pretty, but it should be quite user friendly, and hopefully bug free.\n
        If you don\'t know what Hypixel Skyblock is, the general gist is that it\'s a game where you can collect
        resources, and either use them for yourself or sell them to other players. Hypixel has provided an
        API where you can access the prices of all the items in json form as long as you have your API key, and each individual
        person can access the server up to 120 times a minute with their key (completely reasonable, prevents DDOS)\n
        However, considering a playerbase in the hundreds of thousands, if people actually like my app, it makes sense I couldn\'t just
        use my own key for everyone. But since this is for a demonstration, I\'m not assuming you play the game, so I have provided my key
        for your use. Please try to avoid reloading the app more than 120 times per minute. \n
        If you are sufficiently impressed and want to know more, let me know and I can share the well commented source code with you.\n
        A bit more context if you don\'t actually know what\'s going on in this game:\n
        The game has \"minions\" which produce resources even when you are offline.\n
        They all produce resources at different rates, so this app can read the sell data and tell you which minion
        will produce money at the fastest rate for you.\n
        Since demand is fluid, this app can check the prices for you at the frequency you choose, and send push notifications when prices change
        drastically. Of course, the definition of drastic is up to you, if you think 5% is enough, great, or perhaps you only care when it changes by
        more than 50%, also up to you.
        </string>
    <string name="demo_button_text">I get it, now take me to the actual app</string>
    <string name="view_prices">view current bazaar prices</string>
    <string name="title_activity_view_prices">Bazaar Prices</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="view_prices_settings">Order Prices Will be Displayed</string>
    <string name="arbitrage_settings">Arbitrage Settings</string>
    <string name="alphabetical">Alphabetically</string>
    <string name="by_popularity">By Popularity</string>
    <string name="arbitrage">arbitrage</string>
    <string name="quick_flip_header">Profits from leveraging the difference between the buy and sell price:</string>
    <string name="quick_flip_instructions">\nBasically, if the sell and buy prices are very different, you can create a large buy order at the current price
                and flip it once the order is fulfilled.\n
                WARNING: Does not always work, for example, diamonds could be sell for 10 and buy for 12, and you could buy them for
                10 coins and flip them for 12, thinking you\'ll make 2 profit per diamond, but remember there\'s always a chance that after
                your buy order is filled, the buy price drops to 8, and now you\'ve made a loss. So proceed at your own risk.</string>
    <string name="bazaar_flip">show me the best bazaar flips</string>
    <string name="npc_flip">Profits from selling NPC goods on bazaar</string>
    <string name="npc_flip_help">\nAt NPC shops, you can buy up to 640 of each item per day at a fixed price.\n
                                If that price is lower than the current bazaar sell price, you can buy the item from the NPC and sell it immediately for guaranteed profit.</string>
    <string name="npc_flip_button">show me today\'s profit</string>
    <string name="question_mark">\?</string>
    <string name="prices_last_updated">PRICES LAST UPDATED: </string>
    <string name="bazaar_flip_amount">Maximum buy order amount:</string>
    <string name="european_question">When the United States Supreme Court makes rulings that advance civil rights, which part of the Constitution do they normally
    use as justification for their ruling?\nFurthermore, when the United States Congress needs to make regulations, which part of the Constitution do they use as justification?</string>
    <string name="real_challenge">Tired of puzzle apps pretending to be difficult while in reality anyone with an IQ over room temperature can easily solve it?
    Well here I have provided challenges, some of which do in fact require an IQ at least 2 standard deviations above the norm in order to be able to solve.
    So you should not worry if you can\'t solve some of challenges, they were simply designed for someone far smarter than you.\n
    The features unlocked below this point are all fairly useless, so if you absolutely can\'t figure something out, just do what
    you normals typically do, and just give up.\nHowever, if you do happen to figure it out, there\'s an achievement in it for you.</string>
    <string name="xenobiologist">You are designing a new life form, and in order to ensure your creation doesn\'t mutate out of
    control, you made a modification to normal life as we know it. Instead of a triplet code for protein synthesis, you have adapted
    a quadruplet code. It was quite exhausting to do, so you just let your intern come up with the codons.
    Your intern decided to just go with adding an extra adenine to the end of each of the normal protein codons.
    Too tired to argue, you decided to just go with it. You need to get this organism to synthesize a polypeptide
    that is composed solely of 5 tryptophan in a chain.\n
    From 5\' to 3\', what DNA template strand must exist in this organism in order for the above chain to be synthesized? </string>
    <string name="agreement">Agree to Terms Before Using:\nThis app has been provided to you free of charge. You do not have to pay for any part of this app, the purchases are donations,
    and you do not receive anything extra for giving money besides the satisfaction you get from supporting something that benefits you.
    Furthermore, there will be no ads in this app, if you wanted more reason to support what I do here.
    This app is designed to attempt to give you extra information that may benefit you while you play Skyblock.
        However, the information provided within does not constitute legal trading advice, if you utilize any of the
        information given to you by this app and lose any virtual currency, the author is not responsible for your loss.
    This software was not designed with malicious intent, but the author will not be responsible for any damages to your
     physical device that result from the usage of this app. By clicking agree below, you acknowledge that you use
    this app at your own risk, and you will not hold the author responsible for any damages. If you do not agree
    to these terms, uninstall this app.</string>
    <!--    MIT License-->

    <!--    Copyright (c) 2020 tonkaew131-->

    <!--    Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy-->
    <!--    of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal-->
    <!--    in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights-->
    <!--    to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell-->
    <!--    copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is-->
    <!--    furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:-->

    <!--    The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all-->
    <!--    copies or substantial portions of the Software.-->

    <!--    THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR-->
    <!--    IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,-->
    <!--    FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE-->
    <!--    AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER-->
    <!--    LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,-->
    <!--    OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE-->
    <!--    SOFTWARE.-->
    <string name="minionJSONData">{\"minions\":[{\"name\":\"Cobblestone Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1],\"items\":[\"COBBLESTONE\"],\"npc_val\":[1],\"tier\":{\"1\":14,\"2\":14,\"3\":12,\"4\":12,\"5\":10,\"6\":10,\"7\":9,\"8\":9,\"9\":8,\"10\":8,\"11\":7}},{\"name\":\"Obsidian Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1],\"items\":[\"OBSIDIAN\"],\"npc_val\":[12],\"tier\":{\"1\":45,\"2\":45,\"3\":42,\"4\":42,\"5\":39,\"6\":39,\"7\":35,\"8\":35,\"9\":30,\"10\":30,\"11\":24}},{\"name\":\"Glowstone Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[3],\"items\":[\"GLOWSTONE_DUST\"],\"npc_val\":[2],\"tier\":{\"1\":25,\"2\":25,\"3\":23,\"4\":23,\"5\":21,\"6\":21,\"7\":19,\"8\":19,\"9\":16,\"10\":16,\"11\":13}},{\"name\":\"Gravel Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1],\"items\":[\"FLINT\"],\"npc_val\":[4],\"tier\":{\"1\":26,\"2\":26,\"3\":24,\"4\":24,\"5\":22,\"6\":22,\"7\":19,\"8\":19,\"9\":16,\"10\":16,\"11\":13}},{\"name\":\"Sand Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1],\"items\":[\"SAND\"],\"npc_val\":[2],\"tier\":{\"1\":26,\"2\":26,\"3\":24,\"4\":24,\"5\":22,\"6\":22,\"7\":19,\"8\":19,\"9\":16,\"10\":16,\"11\":13}},{\"name\":\"Clay Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[4],\"items\":[\"CLAY_BALL\"],\"npc_val\":[3],\"tier\":{\"1\":32,\"2\":32,\"3\":30,\"4\":30,\"5\":27.5,\"6\":27.5,\"7\":24,\"8\":24,\"9\":20,\"10\":20,\"11\":16}},{\"name\":\"Ice Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1],\"items\":[\"ICE\"],\"npc_val\":[0.5],\"tier\":{\"1\":14,\"2\":14,\"3\":12,\"4\":12,\"5\":10,\"6\":10,\"7\":9,\"8\":9,\"9\":8,\"10\":8,\"11\":7}},{\"name\":\"Snow Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[4],\"items\":[\"SNOW_BALL\"],\"npc_val\":[1],\"tier\":{\"1\":13,\"2\":13,\"3\":12,\"4\":12,\"5\":11,\"6\":11,\"7\":9.5,\"8\":9.5,\"9\":8,\"10\":8,\"11\":6.5}},{\"name\":\"Coal Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1],\"items\":[\"COAL\"],\"npc_val\":[2],\"tier\":{\"1\":15,\"2\":15,\"3\":13,\"4\":13,\"5\":12,\"6\":12,\"7\":10,\"8\":10,\"9\":9,\"10\":9,\"11\":7}},{\"name\":\"Iron Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1],\"items\":[\"IRON_INGOT\"],\"npc_val\":[3],\"tier\":{\"1\":17,\"2\":17,\"3\":15,\"4\":15,\"5\":14,\"6\":14,\"7\":12,\"8\":12,\"9\":10,\"10\":10,\"11\":8}},{\"name\":\"Gold Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1],\"items\":[\"GOLD_INGOT\"],\"npc_val\":[4],\"tier\":{\"1\":22,\"2\":22,\"3\":20,\"4\":20,\"5\":18,\"6\":18,\"7\":16,\"8\":16,\"9\":14,\"10\":14,\"11\":11}},{\"name\":\"Diamond Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1],\"items\":[\"DIAMOND\"],\"npc_val\":[8],\"tier\":{\"1\":29,\"2\":29,\"3\":27,\"4\":27,\"5\":25,\"6\":25,\"7\":22,\"8\":22,\"9\":19,\"10\":19,\"11\":15}},{\"name\":\"Lapis Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[6],\"items\":[\"INK_SACK:4\"],\"npc_val\":[1],\"tier\":{\"1\":29,\"2\":29,\"3\":27,\"4\":27,\"5\":25,\"6\":25,\"7\":23,\"8\":23,\"9\":21,\"10\":21,\"11\":18}},{\"name\":\"Redstone Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[4.5],\"items\":[\"REDSTONE\"],\"npc_val\":[1],\"tier\":{\"1\":29,\"2\":29,\"3\":27,\"4\":27,\"5\":25,\"6\":25,\"7\":23,\"8\":23,\"9\":21,\"10\":21,\"11\":18}},{\"name\":\"Emerald Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1],\"items\":[\"EMERALD\"],\"npc_val\":[6],\"tier\":{\"1\":28,\"2\":28,\"3\":26,\"4\":26,\"5\":24,\"6\":24,\"7\":21,\"8\":21,\"9\":18,\"10\":18,\"11\":14}},{\"name\":\"Quartz Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1],\"items\":[\"QUARTZ\"],\"npc_val\":[4],\"tier\":{\"1\":22.5,\"2\":22.5,\"3\":21,\"4\":21,\"5\":19,\"6\":19,\"7\":17,\"8\":17,\"9\":14.5,\"10\":14.5,\"11\":11.5}},{\"name\":\"End Stone Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1],\"items\":[\"ENDER_STONE\"],\"npc_val\":[2],\"tier\":{\"1\":26,\"2\":26,\"3\":24,\"4\":24,\"5\":22,\"6\":22,\"7\":19,\"8\":19,\"9\":16,\"10\":16,\"11\":13}},{\"name\":\"Wheat Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1,1],\"items\":[\"WHEAT\",\"SEEDS\"],\"npc_val\":[1,0.5],\"tier\":{\"1\":15,\"2\":15,\"3\":13,\"4\":13,\"5\":11,\"6\":11,\"7\":10,\"8\":10,\"9\":9,\"10\":9,\"11\":8}},{\"name\":\"Melon Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[5],\"items\":[\"MELON\"],\"npc_val\":[1],\"tier\":{\"1\":24,\"2\":24,\"3\":22.5,\"4\":22.5,\"5\":21,\"6\":21,\"7\":18.5,\"8\":18.5,\"9\":16,\"10\":16,\"11\":13}},{\"name\":\"Pumpkin Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1],\"items\":[\"PUMPKIN\"],\"npc_val\":[4],\"tier\":{\"1\":32,\"2\":32,\"3\":30,\"4\":30,\"5\":27,\"6\":27,\"7\":24,\"8\":24,\"9\":20,\"10\":20,\"11\":16}},{\"name\":\"Carrot Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[3],\"items\":[\"CARROT_ITEM\"],\"npc_val\":[1],\"tier\":{\"1\":20,\"2\":20,\"3\":18,\"4\":18,\"5\":16,\"6\":16,\"7\":14,\"8\":14,\"9\":12,\"10\":12,\"11\":10}},{\"name\":\"Potato Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[3],\"items\":[\"POTATO_ITEM\"],\"npc_val\":[1],\"tier\":{\"1\":20,\"2\":20,\"3\":18,\"4\":18,\"5\":16,\"6\":16,\"7\":14,\"8\":14,\"9\":12,\"10\":12,\"11\":10}},{\"name\":\"Mushroom Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[0.5,0.5],\"items\":[\"RED_MUSHROOM\",\"BROWN_MUSHROOM\"],\"npc_val\":[4,4],\"tier\":{\"1\":30,\"2\":30,\"3\":28,\"4\":28,\"5\":26,\"6\":26,\"7\":23,\"8\":23,\"9\":20,\"10\":20,\"11\":16}},{\"name\":\"Cactus Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[3],\"items\":[\"CACTUS\"],\"npc_val\":[1],\"tier\":{\"1\":27,\"2\":27,\"3\":25,\"4\":25,\"5\":23,\"6\":23,\"7\":21,\"8\":21,\"9\":18,\"10\":18,\"11\":15}},{\"name\":\"Cocoa Beans Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[3],\"items\":[\"INK_SACK:3\"],\"npc_val\":[3],\"tier\":{\"1\":27,\"2\":27,\"3\":25,\"4\":25,\"5\":23,\"6\":23,\"7\":21,\"8\":21,\"9\":18,\"10\":18,\"11\":15}},{\"name\":\"Sugar Cane Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[3],\"items\":[\"SUGAR_CANE\"],\"npc_val\":[2],\"tier\":{\"1\":22,\"2\":22,\"3\":20,\"4\":20,\"5\":18,\"6\":18,\"7\":16,\"8\":16,\"9\":14.5,\"10\":14.5,\"11\":12}},{\"name\":\"Nether Wart Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[3],\"items\":[\"NETHER_STALK\"],\"npc_val\":[3],\"tier\":{\"1\":50,\"2\":50,\"3\":47,\"4\":47,\"5\":44,\"6\":44,\"7\":41,\"8\":41,\"9\":38,\"10\":38,\"11\":32}},{\"name\":\"Flower Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[0.8,0.2],\"items\":[\"SMALL_FLOWER\",\"TALL_FLOWER\"],\"npc_val\":[1,2],\"tier\":{\"1\":30,\"2\":29,\"3\":28,\"4\":27,\"5\":26,\"6\":25,\"7\":24,\"8\":23,\"9\":22,\"10\":21,\"11\":20}},{\"name\":\"Fishing Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[0.5,0.25,0.12,0.04,0.03,0.03,0.03],\"items\":[\"RAW_FISH\",\"RAW_FISH:1\",\"RAW_FISH:3\",\"RAW_FISH:2\",\"PRISMARINE_CRYSTALS\",\"PRISMARINE_SHARD\",\"SPONGE\"],\"npc_val\":[6,10,15,20,5,5,50],\"tier\":{\"1\":78,\"2\":75,\"3\":72,\"4\":72,\"5\":68,\"6\":68,\"7\":62.5,\"8\":62.5,\"9\":53,\"10\":53,\"11\":35}},{\"name\":\"Zombie Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1],\"items\":[\"ROTTEN_FLESH\"],\"npc_val\":[2],\"tier\":{\"1\":26,\"2\":26,\"3\":24,\"4\":24,\"5\":22,\"6\":22,\"7\":20,\"8\":20,\"9\":17,\"10\":17,\"11\":13}},{\"name\":\"Revenant Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[3,0.2],\"items\":[\"ROTTEN_FLESH\",\"DIAMOND\"],\"npc_val\":[2,8],\"tier\":{\"1\":29,\"2\":29,\"3\":26,\"4\":26,\"5\":23,\"6\":23,\"7\":19,\"8\":19,\"9\":14.5,\"10\":14.5,\"11\":10}},{\"name\":\"Skeleton Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1],\"items\":[\"BONE\"],\"npc_val\":[2],\"tier\":{\"1\":25,\"2\":25,\"3\":23,\"4\":23,\"5\":21,\"6\":21,\"7\":19,\"8\":19,\"9\":16,\"10\":16,\"11\":13}},{\"name\":\"Creeper Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1],\"items\":[\"SULPHUR\"],\"npc_val\":[4],\"tier\":{\"1\":27,\"2\":27,\"3\":25,\"4\":25,\"5\":23,\"6\":23,\"7\":21,\"8\":21,\"9\":18,\"10\":18,\"11\":14}},{\"name\":\"Spider Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1,0.5],\"items\":[\"STRING\",\"SPIDER_EYE\"],\"npc_val\":[3,3],\"tier\":{\"1\":25,\"2\":25,\"3\":23,\"4\":23,\"5\":21,\"6\":21,\"7\":19,\"8\":19,\"9\":16,\"10\":16,\"11\":13}},{\"name\":\"Tarantula Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[3.16,1,0.2],\"items\":[\"STRING\",\"SPIDER_EYE\",\"IRON_INGOT\"],\"npc_val\":[3,3,3],\"tier\":{\"1\":25,\"2\":25,\"3\":23,\"4\":23,\"5\":21,\"6\":21,\"7\":19,\"8\":19,\"9\":16,\"10\":16,\"11\":13}},{\"name\":\"Cave Spider Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[0.5,1],\"items\":[\"STRING\",\"SPIDER_EYE\"],\"npc_val\":[3,3],\"tier\":{\"1\":25,\"2\":25,\"3\":23,\"4\":23,\"5\":21,\"6\":21,\"7\":19,\"8\":19,\"9\":16,\"10\":16,\"11\":13}},{\"name\":\"Blaze Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1],\"items\":[\"BLAZE_ROD\"],\"npc_val\":[9],\"tier\":{\"1\":33,\"2\":33,\"3\":31,\"4\":31,\"5\":28.5,\"6\":28.5,\"7\":25,\"8\":25,\"9\":21,\"10\":21,\"11\":16.5}},{\"name\":\"Magma Cube Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1.8],\"items\":[\"MAGMA_CREAM\"],\"npc_val\":[8],\"tier\":{\"1\":32,\"2\":32,\"3\":30,\"4\":30,\"5\":28,\"6\":28,\"7\":25,\"8\":25,\"9\":22,\"10\":22,\"11\":18}},{\"name\":\"Enderman Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1],\"items\":[\"ENDER_PEARL\"],\"npc_val\":[10],\"tier\":{\"1\":32,\"2\":32,\"3\":30,\"4\":30,\"5\":28,\"6\":28,\"7\":25,\"8\":25,\"9\":22,\"10\":22,\"11\":18}},{\"name\":\"Ghast Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1],\"items\":[\"GHAST_TEAR\"],\"npc_val\":[16],\"tier\":{\"1\":50,\"2\":50,\"3\":47,\"4\":47,\"5\":44,\"6\":44,\"7\":41,\"8\":41,\"9\":38,\"10\":28,\"11\":32}},{\"name\":\"Slime Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1.8],\"items\":[\"SLIME_BALL\"],\"npc_val\":[5],\"tier\":{\"1\":26,\"2\":26,\"3\":24,\"4\":24,\"5\":22,\"6\":22,\"7\":19,\"8\":19,\"9\":16,\"10\":16,\"11\":12}},{\"name\":\"Cow Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1,1],\"items\":[\"RAW_BEEF\",\"LEATHER\"],\"npc_val\":[4,3],\"tier\":{\"1\":26,\"2\":26,\"3\":24,\"4\":24,\"5\":22,\"6\":22,\"7\":20,\"8\":20,\"9\":17,\"10\":17,\"11\":13}},{\"name\":\"Pig Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1],\"items\":[\"PORK\"],\"npc_val\":[5],\"tier\":{\"1\":26,\"2\":26,\"3\":24,\"4\":24,\"5\":22,\"6\":22,\"7\":20,\"8\":20,\"9\":17,\"10\":17,\"11\":13}},{\"name\":\"Chicken Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1,1],\"items\":[\"RAW_CHICKEN\",\"FEATHER\"],\"npc_val\":[4,3],\"tier\":{\"1\":26,\"2\":26,\"3\":24,\"4\":24,\"5\":22,\"6\":22,\"7\":20,\"8\":20,\"9\":18,\"10\":18,\"11\":15}},{\"name\":\"Sheep Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1,1],\"items\":[\"MUTTON\",\"WOOL\"],\"npc_val\":[5,2],\"tier\":{\"1\":24,\"2\":24,\"3\":22,\"4\":22,\"5\":20,\"6\":20,\"7\":18,\"8\":18,\"9\":16,\"10\":16,\"11\":12}},{\"name\":\"Rabbit Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[1,0.35,0.35],\"items\":[\"RABBIT\",\"RABBIT_FOOT\",\"RABBIT_HIDE\"],\"npc_val\":[4,5,5],\"tier\":{\"1\":26,\"2\":26,\"3\":24,\"4\":24,\"5\":22,\"6\":22,\"7\":20,\"8\":20,\"9\":17,\"10\":17,\"11\":13}},{\"name\":\"Oak Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[4],\"items\":[\"LOG\"],\"npc_val\":[2],\"tier\":{\"1\":48,\"2\":48,\"3\":45,\"4\":45,\"5\":42,\"6\":42,\"7\":38,\"8\":38,\"9\":33,\"10\":33,\"11\":27}},{\"name\":\"Spruce Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[4],\"items\":[\"LOG:1\"],\"npc_val\":[2],\"tier\":{\"1\":48,\"2\":48,\"3\":45,\"4\":45,\"5\":42,\"6\":42,\"7\":38,\"8\":38,\"9\":33,\"10\":33,\"11\":27}},{\"name\":\"Birch Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[4],\"items\":[\"LOG:2\"],\"npc_val\":[2],\"tier\":{\"1\":48,\"2\":48,\"3\":45,\"4\":45,\"5\":42,\"6\":42,\"7\":38,\"8\":38,\"9\":33,\"10\":33,\"11\":27}},{\"name\":\"Dark Oak Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[4],\"items\":[\"LOG_2:1\"],\"npc_val\":[2],\"tier\":{\"1\":48,\"2\":48,\"3\":45,\"4\":45,\"5\":42,\"6\":42,\"7\":38,\"8\":38,\"9\":33,\"10\":33,\"11\":27}},{\"name\":\"Acacia Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[4],\"items\":[\"LOG_2\"],\"npc_val\":[2],\"tier\":{\"1\":48,\"2\":48,\"3\":45,\"4\":45,\"5\":42,\"6\":42,\"7\":38,\"8\":38,\"9\":33,\"10\":33,\"11\":27}},{\"name\":\"Jungle Minion\",\"items_per_action\":[4],\"items\":[\"LOG:3\"],\"npc_val\":[2],\"tier\":{\"1\":48,\"2\":48,\"3\":45,\"4\":45,\"5\":42,\"6\":42,\"7\":38,\"8\":38,\"9\":33,\"10\":33,\"11\":27}}]}</string>

</resources>